解决方法是重写AsyncTask的onPostExecute方法。
The solution is to override the onPostExecute method
他在主线程中运行。
of the AsyncTask. And this runs on the main
我们获得forecast结果的字符串数组，
thread. We received the string array of forecast results,
它是从上面的background方法中作为返回值得来的。
which came as a return value from the do
首先，我们清除ForecastAdapter中所有先前的forecast数据。
in background method above. First, we clear the ForecastAdapter
然后，我们
of all the previous forecast entries. Then we go
向ForecastAdapter中一个一个添加新的forecast数据。
ahead and add each new forecast entry one by
这是触发
one to the ForecastAdapter. This is what ultimately triggers
listview更新的代码。注意，如果你是面向Honeycomb或更高版本的设备，
the listView to update. Note that if you're targeting Honeycomb
你在这能够使用addAll方法，
devices and above, you can use an addAll method here,
因此你不需要将他们一个一个添加。
so you don't have to add them one by one.
你能够只添加一次，并且更新listview一次。
You can just add it once and update the listView once.
一旦你点击refresh按钮，你将看到
Once you hit Refresh, you'll see the weather forecast for
接下来七天内你所在地区的天气预报。尽管我们点击了refresh按钮，
the next seven days for your location. Even though we hit
我们没有任何的verbose日志语句需要打印。
Refresh, we don't have any verbose logging statements being printed
我们不需要他们，因为我们现在有方法
out here. We don't need them anymore, because we have a
去检查我们的代码是否正确，那就是看UI。
way to check that our code is correct by looking at the UI now.